So let's get started with Webpack.
现在我们开始学习 Webpack
First off, I want you to imagine a webpage,
首先 想象一个网页
a fairly normal webpage that you might be building.
一个你可能构建过的普通网页
So let's say it looks something like this and it's just a normal run of the mill webpage.
假设是这样的 这就是一个普普通通的网页
We've got some animations running,
其中有一些动画
some animations that might be coming from
某些动画可能来自
a JavaScript's third party cool animations library.
一个第三方 JavaScript 动画库
There's tons of them out there.
有很多这样的库
So something like that is going on.
继续处理类似这样的事情
We've got some tooltips,
我们显示一些提示
maybe coming from Bootstrap and using the Bootstrap tooltips or models
它们可能来自 Bootstrap 使用 Bootstrap 的提示或模型
or something like that that requires the Bootstrap JavaScript library.
或者类似的需要 Bootstrap JavaScript 库的组件
We've got other interactions,
还有其他的交互
they may be custom,
可能是一些定制化的交互
they may be coming from yet another library.
也可能来自于其他的库
You probably have something like a form or a calculator
可能还有表单或计算器
or something like that that you're writing custom JavaScript for.
或者其他需要编写针对网页定制化的 JavaScript 组件
On top of that,
除此之外
to make our website extra cool,
为了让网站更酷
we've got some parallax going on.
我们还加入了一些视差效果
So we've got elements on the page that are scrolling at
即当你向下浏览页面时
different rates or maybe scrolling in from the sides as you go down the page.
页面的元素会以不同的速率滚动
Who knows what you've got going on?
你可能还有更多的设计
But whatever you have going on,
但是无论你要做什么
it's really cool and we are quickly accumulating libraries that we have to manage.
这真的很酷 同时 我们需要管理的库正在迅速增加
So here, I've got a list of some of the files that you might
这里 我列出一些文件的清单 你可能
have already just building a fairly simple webpage like this.
已经使用它们搭建了像这样的一个非常简单的网页
We've got Bootstrap, a fairly common library that is going to be on most webpages.
有 Bootstrap 一个非常通用的库 很多网页都在使用
But on top of Bootstrap,
但是除 Bootstrap 之外
we're using some of the Bootstrap JavaScript like models and tooltips.
我们还用到了一些 Bootstrap 的 JavaScript 例如模型和提示
Then, we also have this animation library and
然后 还用到了这个动画库
the animation library might have a dependency on another library.
动画库可能还依赖了另一个库
It might require jQuery or react or any number of things.
可能需要 jQuery 或 React 或若干其他库
There's also the parallax library.
此外 还有视差库
The parallax library might also have dependencies and you see how
视差库也可能有依赖项 你会发现
we're beginning to really accumulate libraries that all have to be managed,
我们开始积累越来越多需要管理的库
they have to load in a very specific order.
它们必须按照特定的顺序加载
So this can get really difficult really quickly.
所以管理工作很快就会变得非常困难
I think from Lesson 1,
希望在第一节课
hopefully you've got a good picture,
你就意识到了这个问题
you've gotten to look at
你看了一些专业的网站 以及其中包含的资源数量
So when it comes to what Webpack actually does,
因此 当谈到 Webpack 实际的作用时
we have here a lot of JavaScript files.
这里有很多的 JavaScript 文件
So let's say that these are all the files from
假设这些就是
the previous slide along with any of the custom files that you've written.
上一页幻灯片中由你编写的所有 Javascript
We also have all of your styles.
还有你编写的所有样式
Styles that could be in the form of CSS or SaaS or if there's any of the others.
这些样式可以是 CSS 或 Sass 亦或其他任何形式
We'll talk about those other formats later on in the course.
在本课程的后面 我们会讨论那些其他的格式
But here I can write my JavaScript in
但在这里 我可以编写任意数量的 JavaScript 文件
write my styles in however many different files I like.
可以用我喜欢的任意格式编写样式
Then, Webpack is going to run all of those files
然后 Webpack 会通过加载器和插件来运行这些文件
some plugins and we're going to talk about all of those processes later.
稍后我们会介绍这里涉及到的处理过程
Then, it's going to spit all of those out into a bundle.js file,
然后 Webpack 将所有文件内容输出到一个 bundle.js 文件中
just one giant file that has everything we need in it already organized and it's great.
这是一个很大的文件 把我们需要的一切都组织起来 棒极了
So this is essentially what Webpack does.
Webpack 所做的基本上就是这样
When I think about when do I need Webpack and when do I
当我思考什么时候需要 Webpack
not need Webpack and really what the benefit of it is,
什么时候不需要 Webpack 以及它能带来什么好处时
I don't know about you, but sometimes I go to the grocery store
我会想到这样的场景 有时去杂货店时
and I only have one or two items that I think I'm going to get.
我认为自己只需要买一两件东西
So I don't take a cart or anything like that and I just walk in and I grab items.
所以没有推购物车 直接空手进去拿东西
But then all of a sudden as I'm going through the store,
但是在逛了一圈后 我突然间发现
I start accumulating more.
自己开始越拿越多
I start grabbing things, "All this is on sale."
可能开始拿组合促销商品
So then I get to the end and I'm awkwardly carrying all of these things to the cashier
最终 我走向收银台 尴尬地搬着这些东西递给收银员
and I have to make a decision about whether I want
我必须决定要一个购物袋还是
bags or whether I want to try and awkwardly carry everything to my car.
尝试尴尬地把这些东西搬到车上
Hopefully, like the bagger is going to put everything
希望最后装袋机把所有东西
into well organized bags and in this case,
井井有条地放进袋子 这个示例中
our assets are like all the things that we're buying.
资源文件就像我们购买的东西
You might only really need one or two things.
你可能真正需要的只有一两个资源
So you might not need a build tool
这样 你可能不需要构建工具
that's going to put everything in nice organized bags for you like this.
来将所有东西放进井井有条的 "包裹" 中
But clients never want you to simplify a website.
但是客户从来都不会想要你简单做个网站
As your website grows and as it gets older,
随着网站的不断发展和成熟
you're going to be adding things to it all the time.
你会一直添加新的东西进去
No website stays exactly the same for a really long time.
没有哪个网站会在很长一段时间里保持不变
So when that's happening,
所以当网站需要改变的时候
you need a good way to manage website's assets,
你会需要一种好的方式来管理网站资源
not just at the moment that you're building the app,
不仅只想着构建应用的那一刻
but also for the future.
也要为未来考虑
So even if you think you're only going to use one or two assets,
因此 即使你认为只打算使用一两个资源
I would still lean towards adding a build tool,
我仍然倾向于添加一个构建工具
adding Webpack so that you have a good way to manage those in the future.
添加 Webpack 以便未来有一个好的方式管理网站资源
When we add Webpack,
如果添加 Webpack
we're going to have some really easy bundled files to work with in the end.
最终 我们能得到一些非常简单的打包好的文件
So to put it very simply,
简单来说
what Webpack is allowing us to do is use all of
Webpack 允许我们在开发中以自己想要
our assets the way that we want them in development,
使用的方式使用资源
but then have just one file added to
但是之后只需添加一个文件到
our website head and it makes it a whole lot easier to deal with.
网站的 head 元素中 这让整个过程变得极为简单。最新课程跟课件还有一对一辅导请加wx：udacity6